Okay,
good morning Beijing. Did you have a good
meditation?
[Applause] Do
n't forget the lion dance and
have a Leinster focus.
Very good. Or, this is my plan.
[Music]
I'm going to check if you remember the
software. What we've done so far is very much
from your pivots. Net Team, you have a
way of choosing people's names.
Well, then I'm going to choose the
games. After we review some
works, there are boats. Then I'm going to teach
Tentory, and at 10:30, we'll finish up. We'll enjoy a
book signing. I'll take pictures with you, and
there will be a line here at 10:30.
So have your book ready. If you don't
have money to buy a book, I'll
buy it for you.
[Applause]
Doctor, that's all.
Netcom, let's begin.
Or didn't you
do the mandala this morning? Just
because. So, let's
begin. Are you ready? Let's see the first
picture.
Okay, okay, very good.
And can someone tell me why this
picture is on the cover of your $103 book
and what its name is?  The cover
of his book
and how to make them take up a beautiful place in your mind,
answer and how to make
mobile email because we are going to study how to
make your mind more beautiful, so I chose
this photo, bad decision, this is your
mind is lost, especially the water
and the birds are like little
thoughts that pass through your mind,
Maylis babyphone
in the mind is very good, that's why we are
here, that's what
we are doing,
make a more beautiful mind
for this friend, streaming web,
and what can you tell me about this photo that
is here?
Okay,
element
means, means
that you can
buy a camera with that money to
take many pictures of the Buddha,
which is very
good,
and you also have some very good words,
the second meaning is all the love
of the meta, don't spend more money than
I want, if you have one that touches a
credit card with karma, if it is a
good credit card, it is good to have
a nice house, jumbos, but you must help
other people in
Singapore, otherwise you are just
using and spending money, with a
smart way to use your
credit card and its solution,
Silao, if you use it all just for yourself, I think
Bogotá is giving out that
credit card, it will start  To lower it,
but if you buy something expensive in
Turin, like a Mercedes, but use it to
help Yasmin bring things here,
if you're going to create more good seeds than you
're using,
then it's also... I can have a
luxury car with a client. It's fine to have
nice things, but use them
for good purposes, and Zoric, then
your good seed spirits won't run out.
In this picture,
this is an American woman. She spends
more money than she has,
and she bought the camera, but she didn't take
good pictures,
and after a week, she has fewer
karmic seeds than she
had before.
A very good way to make
good seeds
is to encourage others to reinvest. That's me, okay?
So, your friends, your family, when you
encourage them,
for example, when you buy
nice things for your family, for example, putting
your parents
on a private flight, which is
wrong, but save some for
poor people to do long-term projects, and
then you don't run out of money. Best
Western Mail.
The best way to make extra seeds, to
have extra money in your bank account,
is to encourage others to do something
extra.  The Heartbreak Houston crowd
has a really good tradition;
it's one of their five rules,
and it says that every person, every
income they receive, must
give 5% or 10% to
charity projects. It's a requirement and a
great custom, so we can do the
same if we encourage our friends to
do this. We'll make extra good
beers today. I'm going to ask for
donations for I'm Not
You Can,
and you can give to my charity project,
but even better if you create your own
charity project.
I really like it, so today I'm going to
ask for the older gay charity project,
but it's more powerful if you
do your own project. Every person
here can do their own
charity project. It's easy: set aside
10% and then donate it to whatever
you want.
I like to tell people to use
your mom's name for the charity project.
My mom's real name is Happy
Inside
Like Him, and it means Elizabeth.
I have two great Elizabeths in a
video, but her friends call her Banking. It's kind of like that, so I did
A
charity project called Pong,
and people ask me what a bot is. I say it's
my mom, and you can do the same. It's
your own project. You put in 10%,
and you
can give something, for example, to
the earthquake relief efforts in
China, or
to flamenco dancers in Japan. You don't
decide; that's more powerful.
Also, give a little to my
charity project, which I
explained to you. The following photo...
this is a very profound photograph; it
has a very deep meaning. I think it's
a photo worth $100. It has
two parts. I do
n't know if anyone can guess them.
Is there any brave person who wants to
guess?
Two parts: Your faith
[Music]
1.
You are the one who creates and is creating karma, and you
're not just consuming it. Perfect.
$100.
Who are you going to give the money to? I have it
here in my backpack. A little bit, don't forget.
[Music]
Good answer.
Who wrote a famous explanation
about the Yin Wang Jing? And there are two types
of people.
The first type is like, as if they are
using their karmic seeds, bordering,
as if they are.  Burning, which person
in the picture is burning their
karmic memories, the person on the right is
burning their seeds because they're
having coffee
or something, so you understand, they're not
drinking coffee,
the other person is creating new ones,
those chambers, and they say,
don't be a seed eater,
and so it will be, be
a seed producer, so the
person on the left is producing
seeds, the person on the right
is using seeds,
right? No, the person on the right is
resting. This is one of the best
seeds you can plant: work hard,
serve others, and take a break. I
take it because I'm a real
dharma person, I know how to relax very well, I put on
rock and roll music, have
a delicious coffee, lie down on
the sofa, and eat three pastries from the
restaurant.
Okay, that's what I'm going to do this
afternoon. So a person who practices
bartending has to know the importance of
knowing how to relax, and then you also make
good seeds. I'm going to sit down, I'm going to
burn some good seeds, have
a good coffee,
and I'm going to rest, and then when
I recharge my battery, then I'm going to
help many people.
So I just think I'm just
joking.  The person on the right
is just burning
good seeds, but it's possible she's
like Jasmine or Johnson
[Music].
She works incredibly hard
to prepare for this retreat, and she's very
intelligent. She knows how to
take a good break from fixing your
brain,
and she knows how to relax and
practice rock and roll with Nick Jr. and OK
at 4.
So, rest too.
When you rest, you also create good
seeds.
Next photos:
I think the donkey is the one
running the show
because it slowly passes in the western photo.
100 questions from 100 watts.
Oh, Cabernet.
What does this photo mean? We already
covered it. Take it. Well, there are
three types of suffering.
The third is that people have to
grow old and die,
and nobody pays attention to her because
she's not beautiful anymore. Maybe she used to be
beautiful, but now she isn't.
And she doesn't have money, nor is she young. She
can't do flamenco, so nobody
wants to look. And this happens to
old people, and it means that it will
happen to all of us. A day will come when we will be
old and
alone. Nobody wants to be.  with us at
that moment because we are no longer
fun, we can no longer go and play with
other people, this is the future for
everyone,
and
in bad shopping
this is difficult,
Blasco, guys, I don't,
people in Mexico should know
this, should know,
well, he's not getting nervous,
we talk about this in Mexico, she has
an idea
[Music]
later
do your spiritual practice without stopping
on the eighth floor, continue until you reach
the last floor, if you don't get off, don't get
off before you go up
to the ninth floor because if you haven't
reached in your meditation to
meet your teacher, you haven't
done your meditation well, show me the
first eight levels or floors,
she has it, unfortunately, she has the
answer, it's
just the eight levels, the eight
floors
are just to
warm up, to prepare you,
next picture, this is super easy,
German,
good morning, it's
my pleasure to be here,
this picture means
about Oman and
don't use
these teachings
just to become famous or something like that,
you must really understand their meaning
and use them to
improve yourself, and this is the
meaning
of this picture
and the mantra means that I want to act
like a Buddha, speak like  Buddha and think
like a Buddha and that there is nothing in my
teacher that does not come from me and that my
teacher is like a diamond in the lotus
super perfect
[Applause]
100 dollars for her
[Music]
but
[Applause]
I think we should
also applaud for this tradition
[Applause]
the last one
ok wants to expose this photo needs
explanation
there is a food a dish in America in the
USA which is a vegetable called
eggplant I do
n't know if you have it but Jason Michaels
hates it super-G the super dollar which I
really don't like and when I went to
Paris recently with my partner we
asked our friend Ven Ven
what is a good restaurant here in
Paris
and in the eyes the capul the sister of 6 and they
also sent me a very good restaurant
she lives in Paris so my partner my
partner told me I'm going to order and I
said what do you have and they
brought us this thing and I said what is that
ef
this is
these eggplant
don't give  A good name
that makes it sound better. Don't think I don't
understand what an eggplant is. And Luigi, I
don't want an office, yes.
[Music]
The same garbage is different here, so
why?
So get it
with 100 dollars.
[Applause]
Now we're going to do a new level
and we're going to do it for
about an hour. Okay, we have to
see more things.
The mic, JMR, the Jac,
in kind,
range, who is recording the Under the
Wines and Banking Show.
We think, well, I already understand
that this is samsara. I already understand. I understand
that I'm on the wheel of
rebirth,
but not everything is suffering. And we don't
sing
sometimes. The hotel is going to be a very good
coffee and it's going to taste very good to me and I
enjoy it. So we're in samsara, but
some things are good.
Some things feel good. And then
he says that coffee is also suffering.
It's the lama's answer.
So some things are neutral. There's
grass out there
and I don't attach that much importance to it.
Jasmine never lets me
go outside, so really, well, I do
n't care that much. And that's it.  It's not
suffering,
and in the house it says no, also the
suffering fingers and Marc having the
things that seem like happiness are
intimate suffering.
Even the things we see as
neutral are
also suffering.
If you, for example, burn your hand
while cooking, it's going to
come out like a blister
and it's going to feel bad, it feels hot,
and if you put it under cold water, it's going to
feel okay, it's going to feel good,
but that's just an illusion
because in reality you have a
very ugly blister,
so for a few minutes it's going to
feel good,
but that's your illusion,
nature, that's suffering, the green takeover,
and although it remains to be seen when
you stop the cold water that's touching
the blister, it's going to hurt again.
Journalist P
of Nacho, Nacho, a saying, volcano dance,
for example, this coffee, this is the second
type of suffering, what is its end? The
suffering of the horse, because things
change,
because the seeds run out. The
seed made this coffee, and maybe I don't know,
I used to make a lot of tea for my mom for
many years and seven for me, the most. So
the result has been that that seed
opens and I see coffee on my table.
Someone brought Gueye the coffee and
bought death.  It comes from my seeds, they're going to
avoid it, but every time Howard...
but look, observe, count
1, 2, 3,
and 44 seconds of coffee, 450 seeds
used, used like 250 cups of tea
that I prepared for my teacher. It's a
somewhat difficult business, the
coffee seed business, because it runs out
and maybe I won't have any more coffee, or maybe I wo
n't have a mouth to drink
coffee with. Those seeds also run out
when you use things. You
're using your
white Nissan Sentra mansion.
[Music]
Every experience we have, for example,
when we listen to music, when we spend
time with our children, we're
using seeds all the time, and they'll
change.
Your children will age, then the
music will go bad.
So our body is like
a blister, by its nature, it's
painful. You get a coffee, or you get
a massage, and you feel better for ten
or fifteen minutes.
During the time you get the massage,
your body is aging,
and the massage started at nine in the
morning and ends at ten in the
morning. You feel better, not 200, well.
You had an hour-long massage,
but inside your body is
older now. This is one hour closer to
the thing
that will take your life. So, is the massage
suffering or not?
If it's suffering, you're one hour
closer to cancer.
This is one hour closer to the
heart attack you might have. So, pretend,
pretend to do class. There's
Michael, I'm going to take a break today
because I'm going to get a massage.
But during the message, you're
walking closer to your death. Do you
understand?
Although before the Seleção they'll think that for
me, singing
marched to sell, captured by my 15
years ago.
[Music]
Okay,
Min, it
means that a very important idea is coming,
according to what we have in Shenzhen.
Wow, what is the black Sanskrit for 10
dollars? Well, 20 dollars, 30, 40. Cancel,
said something, won't you see? Why do you have to
speak faster, Nick? What already started
in one means so much that you have no
power.
It's like you're working for a
company and you have a very bad boss.
Maybe you experience this suffering
of having a boss. Very long,
no, Jasmine, because  She's very sweet.
Here
we're talking about a very clear boss,
and this boss comes in 15 minutes,
and after 15 minutes with you, he
says, "There's a
very good job. It's almost
5 o'clock,
and it's almost time for you to go home and
see your family."
And then you say, "But when the boss
says, 'But there's a problem, but we have
a special project,' it's very unusual for
this to happen. I'm not weird about a project,
okay?
If my boss says you have to stay
until 5 in the afternoon, when I was
doing my gay studies at that time,
I made a deal with my boss. I told him
I would take half my salary, but I had to
go home at 5 in the afternoon
because my teacher teaches at 7 in the
afternoon, and it's a two-hour commute to get there on
time. So I made
this agreement. Sometimes my boss would try to
persuade me and say, around
4:45 pm, 'Hey, we have a very special project.
You have to stay past 5,
you have to stay until 7 in the
afternoon,' and I would say, 'No, that's not an
agreement,'
and he would look at me like that
and tell me, 'No,' to everyone.  You like working
here, right? And I was saying, "I like
working here, yes, but okay, if I fire you,
no, like, we're going to fire you." And I said, "I
wish you were fired, I'm going to go
clean my desk now." And he said, "Okay,
go home." In English, we say it like
the game of chicken, but he'll tell me how I'm
going to fire you. And I said, and I was saying, "I'll get there
first," if he was
serious or not. And I was saying, "Then
he learned to be
smarter, please." And your boss
tells you at 4:45 pm and doesn't call you to
his office,
and you don't know, in this company,
Victoria, you're the big boss.
Without you, we're lost, we won't know
what to do. And
only you can do this special project,
you're a special person. And if you
go home,
we'll all win.
You took me, I'll stay, tourism,
with him, okay, see you
here, okay, here's the work. You
know why I'm talking about this? It
means we don't have
the boss, we have power, we have to
do what the boss tells us. If
you work for someone else, they have
the power.  And you don't have it
because we're talking about this, not work.
It's special right now.
The book is going to go in
a very special direction to
explain power. Who has the power?
Right,
Fabiola, who's the boss in your life? Right, who's the boss
in your life? Your
firm, sports. And there are two very famous bosses:
their wives.
Well, actually there are three. The first is
this wife.
The second is karma.
And the third is your negative emotions.
Bukis is going to explain my experience.
Now the book is going to give a long
explanation
about all the types of
negative emotions: anger, jealousy, desire,
pride,
and misunderstanding. How all this is
garbage in the mind, and if we can
clean it up, we'll have a very
beautiful mind. But right now our minds
aren't so beautiful. There's a lot of garbage, and it
pollutes them.
So he's going to explain, and he's going to spend a
lot of time talking about this,
and we're going to go there.
[Music]
I'm going to go.
He has a little more to say about
suffering.
What a shame, so much realism.
Today I went out and saw some people
enjoying the sea, and I told my
friends, "Let's go outside and enjoy some wine," and
then...  You go to the beach and for 50
minutes it's very pleasant,
and then your skin starts to burn, and you think, "I think
I'd
like to go back to my room now."
So you go to your room, and it's very
pleasant; there's no heat, it's not
hot inside, everything is very pleasant.
And after two hours, you get bored; you'd
like to go outside and get some
fresh air. So you go back outside
into the sun, and you think, "It's quick, it's so
nice, I love being in Thailand." And
after two hours in the sun, it's very
hot; you'd like to go back. So
this is the story of our lives.
When the suffering started while you
were outside,
when did it start? I
ask you, when did the
discomfort begin? At what point did you go outside? No,
Gays and Michael, but the first two
hours were very pleasant. No, the
suffering just kept increasing, but you do
n't notice it. There's
a very famous story about Skye or
Waterloo Road,
and a person was walking
along a path and saw a man
banging his head against a
wall. The man said to him, "Don't stop
doing that. Why do you do it? Because it
feels very..."  Well, when I stop, you
understand,
and you walk under the sun, and the
suffering begins, but you don't notice it, and it
just starts to get bigger and
bigger until you finally decide.
Our life is like that; suffering grows
and diminishes and grows and diminishes all the
time. I came, you won't be happy in
any way; you don't have the capacity to
be happy because you have bad seeds; you
are under the power of two
very bad bosses: your past karma
and your past negative emotions are
connected.
When I was 26, I was in the
monastery for about 5 or 6 years,
and I'm the only monk who knows how to
drive a car. So a
great lama came up to me and said, "Hey,
could you drive the car?" And I said, "Yes, I
can."
And he told me that when you get in the
car, and this very
important lama gets in, don't talk to him. And I said...
Why? Because he's the real diamond, of
course, the destroyer of death, the one who
destroys death.
30 eyes,
four faces, long, big teeth, so
don't talk to him, okay? Okay,
then it was time to drive. It
was like a three-hour drive, I mean, to
a place, and three very important lamas
got into the car and sat down.
He, the sea, the blue sea, the
destroyer of death, sat next to
me, and I was like, there's a lady who
was in the back who's still alive. He's 96
years old. She
told me on the other side, "He's
learning a lot, and he's
learning to forget
what Stanley is going to teach."
And the lama, they call him, "Here," he
told me. "It means I was
lucky because I had studied it just
the day before." I said, "This is
the second chapter," and he said, "
What does this mean?" And I didn't know. So, we're
driving, and he
asked me how old I am. I'm
supposed to say 26,
but I was so scared that I said 62
because I was speaking in tongues.
Then he started laughing. "
26,
choose good words, you're going to live a
long life. Keep
driving." So I kept driving
and tried not to talk.
In the back of the car,
the two lamas who were there fell
asleep,
and he called me Taca Peru. He told me, and I said, "
When you drive, we drive. I've
never been to the US. Tell me what
all these things are."
So we arrived at our place,
and he asked me, "What is this? Is this
a cemetery?
Well, when people die, they
dig a hole and bury them underground.
Well, this time, what a waste of space."
And he said, "The car is too hot.
Turn on the air conditioning." And I said, "Even
in 5 minutes,
Westwood, the car is too green,
cool. Turn off your air conditioning. Too
hot, too cold,
too hot, too cold."
And if you think I'm crazy, no, no, no, no, no, no, you
're not crazy.
Then we talked for about two
hours and had a very funny conversation,
and I'll never forget it.
But after that,
for many days, I wondered why he did that
with the air conditioning in our car.
Crazy,
but it seemed like he was. And
the great lamas are always
trying to teach you something. So I
thought he was trying to teach me
with the air conditioning
when I found this teaching in
hunger.
I realized that he was teaching me
this. He was teaching me this.  Part of
observing those things they call you "you get married" because they're going to teach you a
lesson. In
my teacher's car, when we were driving,
he would tell me to turn left, and I
knew it was
the wrong direction. And I would say, "
Well, why
turn left? Maybe I should
turn right," and a big success, I
could crash. He's
talking to you about air
conditioning. It's the
same when you sit for a long
time in class.
We've been sitting for a long time, and then
your friends say, "Let's walk on
the beach.
My butt hurts. We've been
sitting for a long time,"
and you really want to sit down. And
then you sit down, but after
30 minutes, your butt starts to feel
uncomfortable again. The body, which I call
a problem, this body can't make you
happy; it always wants something more.
So the problem, by the way, someone asked
me a question yesterday in
Galicia.
They said, "Oh, my cough has gotten worse." You always say
that we should act like superheroes,
like Iron Man or Superman, and
yesterday you said in class that these
superheroes are just more people who are
suffering and burning out,
consuming all their good karma. So...  Well, the
correct thing to do is to have them from two
types of superheroes,
so sorry if I confused you. I'm
using
movie stars as superheroes as
examples to explain those
powerful people who don't understand the
pen. I live on disc, like people who
have a lot of money in this world and do
n't understand about the pen. I'm just
using them as examples. So
these weeks when I say superhero, I
mean powerful people or people with a
lot of money but who don't get the
joke. So they're actually
consuming their seeds and not
creating new ones.
We teach how to use the seeds
to make money, to have a
happy marriage,
how to use the seeds to have
health,
and to make
a mind full of foundation. But if you don't
know how to create these seeds, you have
a good marriage and your body
is strong and healthy, and nobody around
knows how to make good seeds, and you do
know how to make the seeds, well, you
feel bad because your friends don't know
how to do division. It's like when you
go to a restaurant because you have
money and you buy a very Japanese scene,
but nobody else can afford the image.
Well, imagine everyone is looking out the
window and they're hungry,
and you're eating alone. I gave up on living,
and many people  Poor people are looking
out the window, that's captivity, it's
funny, it feels uncomfortable, people are vulnerable,
looking at you, IB3 in Landete,
a delicious dish,
so being successful is just for you, it
feels lonely, so you want to
share it with other people.
There are two methods, and one method is to
teach them and take them to Thailand,
talk, talk, talk.
This is a method to teach
people about success. The second
method
is just being successful, it's a lot of money
because they have a beautiful partner,
the ballet, when they are 65 years old, they have a
mind full of peace, it's like
advertising for humans, so
people are going to approach you. Today,
Stanley, how do you do so much from scratch? Where did
you get this beautiful partner? And you
also look very healthy, what's your
secret?
[Music]
That's an example, living in the first place, he's
a living example. In Spanish, I
saw people,
living examples, something like that. Why are we
talking about this?
Because we like these
superhero movies, because we like them so much.
[Music]
Ironman can save the whole world.
That stupid kid, what was his name,
Charles Fowler, the one from Transformers, and how did he
come in the movie?  From Transformers
Part 1,
he's like a really dumb kid. He
works for a courier company
and he meets the three main
paths. The 50 with which he gets the
blonde girlfriend, the fastest car, and saves
the whole world. Most important: first,
the girlfriend; second, the
car. Well, also active, and the car
also saved the whole world. Not seeing
how many times the football Transformers
Part 1, Part 2, 43. Why do they
keep making these movies?
Because people like them. Because
people like them
because they want to be the kid who saves the
world. And they also want to give
the girlfriend and the car
things while enjoying the movie.
They also want to be superheroes. So
all of us in our lives,
when we're 10 or 12 years old, Edwards,
we ask
ourselves, why am I here? Why is
this world here?
Why was I born where I was born? One of his posts, what am I supposed to
be? And we
feel hungry. There are
three things we're
hungry for in this life. The first is
food. The second is sex.
We all like sex. What matters is coming. It comes
knowing that it matters. It comes.
million women are  Looking for 3
million pesos, 3 billion
men are looking for 3 billion
women.
This is more nature, but there is a
third water. I want to save the world, like I
want to help all people, and it is
stronger than the desire for food, it is
stronger than the desire for sex, and
all people have it. If
you learn about the feather, and if you use it,
PSUV and conflicts to become
a successful person, you can beat
Spider-Man, you can be better than Spider-
Man and Iron Man,
you will be the Transformer,
part 40. Do you understand? So
this is the second meaning
of superhero. First, at least the first
meaning is almost everything that
those people who don't know about the
joke are, people with a lot of money but they do
n't know about the feathers and they will just age,
die, and lose the money.
Second, superhero
in the feather, superhero by the ass
because they know how to reinvest the
seeds
and they know how to help other people. That is what this is what
I mean
when I say a super, the superhero of the
feather. You must be the superhero of the
feather, not in principle. You must not be the
other superheroes who are very powerful
and die.
Those are the prepared superheroes.
I'm here, I thought to myself, okay,
we need to do more than 20 more minutes. I
know you're tired, that hole to
shoot yourself, that it hurts, withered buttocks.
My boss
then calls me the loneliness of signs, bye. I
know you're tired, you've been
sitting for a long time,
the room is very cold and sometimes it's very hot,
Piet City, and dance,
you have to have a break to go to the
bathroom,
and then he says, "But I don't mind
taking care of your lemons, we have 20 minutes, rather,
I'm seven wires." The problem is
the body and the mind
when we are reborn,
we take another mind, and another is which one
I put by Julian Dindart, like when
you land at the airport,
to the place where you rent cars, and they're going to
give you a car like this owner, support that he
gave, so when you are reborn they give you
a body and they give you a mind of
varying age, to his problem, and that body has
a problem, actually, Miguel 'Happy', you ca
n't make it happy, air
conditioning, you're going to learn, it's
not learning to pay, you're going to go to the
beach, you're going to come back, you're going to go to
Thailand for vacation, and then that one
comes back to Valencia because you like it at
home.  It will make you travel,
nor is the mind... I applied for
a new job. It's a great
electronics company. It's the number one company. To
work, so you and I hope to
come. That's
the power of work. If I made it, I have the job. To
dinner to celebrate. Six
weeks later, I
have to work. My boss...
This is nature. I met a
new guy
and he liked me a lot. What's coming is very
lucky. Six weeks after
biting and having dispensed with a hate
more than any other person in this
world... Ex-wife, ex-wife, it's
not the person, it's
not the job, it's our own mind
of... faulty pactiv, Blake torment card,
cash when you rent a car, in
the rented cars, they give you a
car, a faulty car,
and you can't be happy. It's impossible to be
happy in this body and in this mind.
You will always want to go... longing in the
sun, and you will always want games. You will
always want the guy, and then you wo
n't want him, but it's not the guy. I'm
going to tell you a very
interesting experiment, and you can try it with...
interrupted by...
go to a room with ten people
where there are ten other people after
work. After an hour in front of Wall
Milky, they're going to...  You like three of them,
Wonderland. You wo
n't like three of them, and you wo
n't care about four of them.
3, 3, and 4.
Now take the three you like
and take seven more you like.
Put them in a room and spend an hour
with them. After an hour, it will be
between three you like,
three you don't like,
and four you don't care about. It's
not the
people, it's your mind. Your mind is the de
facto one. 3, 3, and 4. Then from the factory,
your mind
always comes. Even a donkey, a flying one, and it has
taken a living body. The potential, and
people will put things on it and they're going
to hit it. And this is the nature
of its body to be macho for me.
While it's in action, the
cloud team, the glove,
once you get a body, something will happen,
something will happen to it, and that's it.
Even a rose thorn is my
little pain. All day long it will come. I didn't have
little pains, they will come all day long.
It's a problem the
body has because you have a damaged body
that you haven't been able to make happy. You can't make
this body happy.  This
happy mind is defective, it breaks down because it's the
wrong body. We enter the
wrong body and it's very difficult to get out
of it. Okay, well,
not
in Michelle's case. She caught urban corny 700f.
If you take,
for example, many needles and put them in
a bag and put it on
Stanley's back, some of these
needles, or the first ones, will hurt him, and until he takes off
this bag, it will hurt.
But if you were born in this body
and things will come back, it will hurt
until the day you die. We must change
bodies
like when you take off your shirt. We have to get
rid of this body, and you can
do it. It's possible.
You can be an animal,
get a new model, a good model, a
Buddha's body, like the
fashionable body.
My Christian friends come to visit me
at the monastery,
and I took them to the temple so they could see it
because it's so beautiful. And my friend looked all around,
and when we walked away and
left the temple,
Gisela said to me, "I don't understand why you're a
Buddhist." And I said, "What's the
problem?"
And she said, "Those doubts, who
wants to be like that?"  And I said, what's wrong
with doubts? They have, like, the point
on the head, and very long ears
don't look very good. Because you're a Buddhist,
you have to understand that sometimes I
tell my students, "Go bye." If you
're a woman, I say, "Go buy yourself a
magazine, wow,
the V Magazine fashion magazine." And I tell her, "
Pick the most beautiful woman you see
there, the most beautiful model, and that's who you're going to be."
When she moves on, I
tell men, "I'm going to buy the
most famous men's magazine, the most
attractive model, and you're going to be him." When you
become fashionable, you're going to have the
most beautiful body you can imagine, super
beautiful, and you can't die, and you never
feel pain. You
never have to go to the bathroom; you save a
lot of time.
Men don't have to shave
all the time.
With your face and body, so I think, "I do
n't want the hardware." I'm missing something on my
head. I do
n't want to be fat. How is security?
No, it's not like that. We're going to be the
step in the most exquisite and
elegant body you can imagine, and there's no
suffering, no pain. So
we have to change this body because it's
even done through yoga, and  You eat
healthy food, it's still
a problem, getting old will
give you cancer, so we want to
change it, okay, okay, they're living pop art.
Some people say, "Poa poa,
Gisela, don't worry, you can do it
because when you die you say
a special prayer and at that moment you
go to a purple body. It's possible
for one person, for one
person out of a million,
only one person. It
can be that you can wait
until the last minute, which I prepared,
and get your body from a thumb, but it's
very dangerous.
99 percent of people fail, so take
care now. You have to go hunting in
Thailand in two days, so pack
your bags today and enjoy yourself
for two more days. If you don't have to think about it,
and get insurance in the body of a Buddha
now,
and don't wait until the last day of your life
because that will probably
fail.
So change your body now. Learn
how to change your body now. We
call it a living diamond.
Boris, you must take the body, it's a living diamond.
YouTube, YouTube, how to
get that body.
If there is a very special seed, what is
the seed? If coaching for  To see
emptiness directly, Cox, and to see
emptiness directly at that moment, at
that moment
when you get cancer. I have a friend
who is very sad, and she knew—well, she's
a beautiful person—
and she has breast cancer, and some cells started to grow, they
broke,
and it started to break uncontrollably,
and then inside the body is
rotting, like an
old banana. On the outside it looks fine,
and since the sun hadn't come out yet, I couldn't
see very well. And April, I
wanted to eat it, but it tasted very bad. On the outside it looks
fine, but inside
it's bad. That's how cancer is. The skin is still there,
but inside there's something that's creeping along,
deteriorating. Very sad,
and in fact, you can't stop it. And if it
starts,
you can slow the process, but you can't
stop it.
But if you perceive emptiness, it's the
opposite. One cell becomes a
diamond, and then two cells
become a living diamond, and so on.
Because at that moment,
when you directly perceive emptiness,
the body is received like a
cancer, pubic cancer, and your body
started to change, and nothing can stop it. There's
no cure for cancer.  Buddhist teachings
begin with a single cell, it will
expand, and your body will
become immortal and very beautiful,
without pain.
Your experiences and loved ones
can also learn. If you
directly perceive emptiness, this process
begins, the process stops, and you cannot
stop it. And
before, I even had a situation
about emptiness. It
makes a change within you; you can no longer
go down to hell if something changes
within you. That's why
we teach the feather over and over again.
We have a Voyager class
for children, and I ask them what the
nicest thing their mother did for them is. They
all said different
things, and then I told them that the
nicest thing that exists is what your mother did for you.
I think one child said, "I taught my
mother about the feather."
[Music]
That was incredible.
By the way, those children know about the
four steps very well, so I think
their parents are doing a very good
job.
[Applause]
Aitor, the sporting one,
taught a class for children for 15 years. I did it
as a confession
because I had an abortion when I was
in college. I was
a Buddhist, so I didn't understand it, and
then I...  I told my teacher that when I
was younger I participated in an abortion and
he said you have to
cleanse this seed. I asked him
how to cleanse this seed.
I think you destroyed a child, so you have to
teach the children. I asked him
for how long? He said until the
seed has been verified. And I asked how
long is that? He
said, "
Your heart will feel happy when
that seed is gone. Your heart will
feel much more changed. Until
then your heart will feel
heavy and I haven't realized it, but I know it
in my heart." And I realized he
was right. I felt sad
inside, so I said what do I have to
do? Maybe I'll
teach a class for the
children.
So I started a class for children with the children's
parents, with the CAC, with
their parents' permission. The children came
to the class, so I taught them
about the seeds. I taught them the
four steps
of working on this.
There's a story because it's
very hot in the summer in our country.
And usually, New York is very, very, very
nice because it's on the ocean, but in
the summer it's very hot, there's a lot of
humidity, and we use air conditioning.
So I am  Teaching the children,
I taught for 15 years
until I felt change. 15 years passed.
One day, the air conditioner was broken,
and I had to
go up some stairs to
fix it. A child was pulling down my
pants, and I said, "Stop!
I'm fixing the
air conditioner!" He kept pulling at my
pants, and I said, "Stop!"
The Uruguayan teacher said, "What?
And Sukkur? And what are you doing?
I'm fixing the air conditioner
because it's too
hot inside.
That's not the way to fix an air
conditioner. So what's the way?
You go outside and find someone else
whose air conditioner is broken and
fix it.
[Applause]
And if you hear, the air conditioner
won't stop working today. [
Laughter]
Here,
children learn better than the adults
who used to send them on foot.
This fund costs...
[Applause] That's how it is,
Ochoa.
[Music]
Queen, next link,
what
blood without your mind.
[Music]
You walk,
I pass
life  Urbana sends the stretcher, shut up,
what's up, and what about
the nobodies? Giorgi
are kings of the show,
so bad
and few,
okay?